http://www.safety-software.co.uk/about-us/privacy-policy

SolutionsAbout UsAirswebPartnersCareersBenefitsPrivacy PolicyData ProtectionCustomersResourcesBlogNewsEventsCase StudiesFree ResourcesInnovationContactAIRSWEBPrivacy PolicyAbout Our Privacy PolicyAirsweb takes your privacy seriously. Your personal information will not be sold or otherwise distributed to third parties without your consent. Airsweb is not a source of unsolicited email.What Our Privacy Policy CoversThis policy covers what personal information Airsweb collects, how that information is collected and why we need it. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not cover the practices of companies other than Airsweb or people who are not employed or managed by Airsweb. Third party sites provide the products and services listed on Airsweb and these sites have their own privacy statements and are not covered by this policy.What Information We Collect and How We Use ItProviding your email address to Airsweb is optional and used solely to update you with new products and services that our site has to offer, or to respond to queries you have sent. Airsweb automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, browser type, and the page(s) you request. This information is collected anonymously and is used to better understand how people use our site and improve its performance.Who Has Access to Your InformationAs a matter of policy Airsweb does not sell, rent, share or otherwise distribute any of your personal information to third parties except in certain specific circumstances. Those circumstances are as follows:1. We receive a subpoena, court order or other legal demand for your information.2. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or as otherwise required by law.3. Airsweb is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event Airsweb will notify you before your information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.4. Some of our services allow you to make certain information public or accessible to certain individuals. If you make use of these services Airsweb will share your information as you request.What are Cookies and Why do We Use ThemCookies are a standard Internet technology, and many major web sites use them to provide useful features for their members. Cookies allow us to store and retrieve login and other information on a user’s system. They provide us with data that we can use to improve our service to you. Cookies themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user’s computer. The default setting for most browsers is to accept cookies; if you prefer you can set yours to refuse them. If you choose not to accept cookies you will not be able to take full advantage of Airsweb.What Happens if Airsweb Makes a Change to This Policy?If Airsweb intends to make a change to our privacy policy we will post a notice on this site and we will also notify you by email.How You Can Contact UsIf you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website or your dealings with this website you may get in touch with us through the Contact Us page.How to UnsubscribeIf you no longer wish to receive updates on the products and services that we offer then please send an email from that address with the word “unsubscribe” in the subject.ProductSolutionsArrange a DemoAbout UsAirswebCustomersPartnersBecome a PartnerCareersContactNewsBlogNewsEventsCase StudiesLegalSite MapData Processing PolicyCookie PolicyCOVID-19 Return to work risk assessment V2COVID-19 Premise based staff risk assessment V2COVID-19 Mobile staff risk assessment V1AccreditationsJoin The Airsweb Mailing ListNameEmail AddressThank you! You are subscribed!Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.All rights reserved airsweb® 1999 to 2020. Registered in England. Registered Office: Rockland House, View Road, Rainhill, Prescot, Merseyside, L35 0LG Company Registration Number: 04160275Brochure RequestTo download a brochure please provide us with your details in the short form below. We won't share your information with anybody else, it is private and secureFirst NameSecond NameEmailPhoneCompanyCountryTick to receive more information from Airsweb. Read our Data Processing Policy for how we may contact you.Download BrochureYour brochure request has been submitted to Airsweb successfully. Click the link below to download your Airsweb brochure directly to your device.Begin Download...Oops! Something went wrong while submitting the form.CloseDownload BrochureDownload Brochure
